[{"id": 1146, "question": "Thousands of people living in the Chinese capital will celebrate the start of the Chinese New year by heading for the ski resorts . Never mind that Beijing's dry weather seldom produces snow. It is cold enough in winter for snow-making machines to make a covering for the hills north to the capital. And the rapid growth of a pleasure-seeking middle class has formed the basis for this new craze . Since Beijing's first ski resort was opened ten years ago, the sport has enjoyed astonishing increase. There are now more than a dozen resorts. Clothes markets in the city have added bright colored ski suits to their winter collections. Mr. Wei, a manager of a newly-opened ski resort in Beijing, sees the growth of an industry that could soon lead Chinese to head for the ski resorts of Europe. In rec...\n\nQ: Why are some Chinese likely to go skiing in Europe?", "options": ["To visit more ski areas.", "To ski on natural snow.", "For a large collection of ski suits.", "For better services and equipment."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2102, "question": "Expressions about water are almost as common as water itself. The expressionto be in hot water is a very old expression. Hot water was used five hundred years ago to mean being in trouble. One story says it got that meaning from the custom of throwing extremely hot water down on enemies attacking a castle. That no longer happens. But we still get in hot water. When we are in hot water, we are in trouble. It can be any kind of trouble--serious or not so serious. A person who breaks a law can be in hot water with the police. A young boy can be in hot water with his mother, if he walks in the house with dirty shoes. Beingin deep wateris almost the same as being in hot water. When you are in deep water, you are in a difficult position. To keep your head above wateris a colorful expression that...\n\nQ: The passage explains the origins of the following expressions EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["to be in hot water", "to keep your head above water", "water over the dam", "to hold water"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2869, "question": "New York Times---( DINITIA SMITH )Tomorrow is the 433d anniversary of Shakespeare's birth. A recent survey shows that more people are watching him, reading him and studying him than ever before. Consider the recent yearly conference of the Shakespeare Association of America in Washington, where more than 600 people who study or admire Shakespeare from 18 countries took in topics like ''Whither Attribution Studies,'' ''Unpopular Shakespeare'' and ''Sex Me Here,'' a talk on breast-feeding and Lady Macbeth. ''The national media is saying that fewer students' taking Shakespeare,'' Barbara Mowat, the editor of The Shakespeare Quarterly, observed in a speech at the conference. ''But Shakespeare is thriving.'' The association's membership has increased by a third since 1990. The Shakespeare busin...\n\nQ: Why people from 18 countries came to Washington this year?", "options": ["To celebrate Shakespeare's 433d birth day only.", "To watch some plays by Shakespeare as planned.", "To celebrate Shakespeare's birthday and study his works.", "To discuss how to teach students using Shakespeare's plays."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 449, "question": "Good Teachers A language training school at Yayuncun needs two full-time teachers and three part-time teachers to teach adults, 12 students a class, oral English and business English during afternoons and evenings. Full-time teachers 25--30 hours per week, 10 000--2 000 yuan per month. Part-time teachers can choose the class to teach, 100--150 yuan per hour, according to your experience. Need native English speakers with teaching experience. Please send your RESUME and PICTURE to eslchina@ yahoo.com.cn Writers/Researchers Currently, Fisher's Travel SOS is looking for the freelance writer and researcher with experience in journalism and the ability to computers, it is part-time positions for our project that will take a month to complete. Work is conducted at home, and will take a couple of...\n\nQ: As a salesman, you need to love keeping the customers pleased because  _", "options": ["you are always very friendly to others", "you would like to make friends with them", "you want to sell more products to them", "you have learned a lot of experience"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 929, "question": "London Heathrow is the biggest airport in the UK, and it also handles more international passenger traffic than any other airport in the world. For this reason, enlargement was planned and on 27th March a fifth terminal opened to help to deal with the many passengers that pass through the airport. The new terminal has taken a long time to plan and build. The idea was first proposed back in the 1980s. The opening of it has been talked about widely in the media in the UK and expectations were high for the PS4.3 billion project. However, in spite of long preparations at Terminal 5 ahead of the grand opening, things soon went into a mess. There were problems from the very beginning as staff had difficulties finding car parking spaces and getting through security to get into the building. This ...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["People expected too high for London Heathrow Terminal 5.", "Something went wrong on the very first day of the opening.", "Staffs were complaining about the shamble in the day.", "The British Airline was the only airline operating at Terminal5."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2500, "question": "Alaska's Arctic lakes now freeze later and melt earlier in the year than in 1950,leaving them easy to suffer water loss from evaporation and possibly adding to local warming,a new study finds.The winter ice season near Barrow,Alaska,is shorter than in 1950,researchers reported Jan.30 in the journal The Cryosphere. Lake ice is also thinner each winter.The scientists surveyed 402 lakes on the North Slope,where permafrost (permanently frozen ground)and shallow lakes dominate the areA. In 2011,the lake ice was 38 percent thinner than in 1950,and 22 percent fewer lakes froze through to their bottoms. \"When we saw the actual numbers we were shocked at how dramatic the change has been,\"lead study author Cristina Surdu,of the University of Waterloo in Canada,said in a statement.Surdu and her co-au...\n\nQ: What does the text mainly tell us?", "options": ["Arctic 1akes now freeze earlier and melt 1ater.", "Alaska's local warming is decreasing sharply.", "Arctic lakes are losing ice.", "Arctic lakes hold more flesh water than before."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 516, "question": "In 2005,the American artist Richard Prince's photograph of a photograph,Untitled(Cowboy),was sold for $1 248 000. Prince is certainly not the only contemporary artist to have worked with so-called \"found photographs\"--a loose term given to everything from discarded prints discovered in a junk shop to old advertisements or amateur photographs from a stranger's family album.The German artist Joachim Schmid,who believes \"basically everything is worth looking at\",has gathered discarded photographs,postcards and newspaper images since 1982.In his on-going project,Archiv,he groups photographs of family life according to themes:people with dogs;teams;new cars;dinner with the family;and so on. Like Schmid,the editors of several self-published art magazines also champion found photographs.One of th...\n\nQ: According to the passage,Joachim Schmid  _  .", "options": ["is fond of collecting family life photographs", "found a complaining note under his car wiper", "is working for several self-published art magazines", "wondered at the artistic nature of found photographs"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 584, "question": "Dear Ms Morris, We have come to know of an unfortunate incident you had with our customer service department and we would like to deeply apologize for the inconvenience caused to you by the customer service manager's behavior. We have noted down your complaint (number 797329SA) and would like to let you know that strict action will be taken against the employee. He is a new employee with little experience and so his attitude towards his job was over enthusiastic and he lacked proper judgment. We are by no means excusing his behavior but I would like to request you not to take any legal action against the company as we are very sorry for what happened. To express our appreciation, please accept the offer of free servicing of all products of our company that you own for up to three years. We...\n\nQ: What do the two letters have in common?", "options": ["Both complain about poor services.", "Both are written to make an apology.", "Both explain how to use the product.", "Both discuss how to make up for the loss."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2420, "question": "Recently I have discovered it's often easier for me to do something every day than to do it just some days. I post to my blog six days a week. I take notes every day. I write in my one-sentence journal every day. Many people have told me that they find it easier to exercise when they exercise every day. If I try to do something just four days a week, I spend a lot of time arguing with myself: Is today the day, or is it tomorrow, or the next day? Does the week start on Sunday or Monday? If you do something every day, you tend to fall into a routine. Routine has a bad reputation for lacking excitement. It's true that novelty and challenge bring happiness and that people who break their routines, try new things, and go to new places are happier, but I think that some routine activities also b...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements does Andy Warhol probably agree to?", "options": ["Doing something that is exciting.", "Doing something almost every day.", "Doing something every day, not only once.", "Doing something every day or only once."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1400, "question": "An air of anxious uncertainty spread throughout the small Indian camp as the sun dawned that morning. Some braves gathered beside a smoking campfire. Murmuring sounds could be heard as they talked quietly. Women nervously performed their domestic tasks, preparing a small meal. Several sad, old men sat mute, their morale very low. The camp was pitched at the edge of a deep valley--so deep that one could barely see the calm water at the bottom. The Indians had been taken by surprise and were surrounded and attacked by enemy forces. They fought bravely, but they were degraded by defeat. Their homes were destroyed. Those who had survived had been pursued by the enemy. The chase had lasted for days. Persuaded by their leaders to press on, they had made a wrong turn. Their _ journey ended at the...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["Both the defeated Indians and their enemies believed the bridge was provided by the Great Spirit.", "The stone bridge is no longer in existence.", "The defeated Indians had been pursued by the enemy for several days.", "The Indians in the camp were in a serious situation because they took a wrong course."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 483, "question": "I recently turned fifty, which is young for a tree, midlife for an elephant, and ancient for a sportsman. Fifty is a nice number for the states in the US or for a national speed limit but it is not a number that I was prepared to have hung on me. Fifty is supposed to be my father's age, but now I am stuck with this number and everything it means. A few days ago, a friend tried to cheer me up by saying, \" Fifty is what forty used to be.\" He had made an inspirational point, Am I over the hill?People keep telling me that the hill has been moved, and I keep telling them that he high-jump bar has dropped from the six feet I once easily cleared to the four feet that is impossible for me now. \" Your are not getting older, you are getting better.\" says Dr. Joyce Brothers. This, however, is the kin...\n\nQ: The author considers his fifty years of life", "options": ["peaceful", "ordinary", "satisfactory", "regretful"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 602, "question": "STRANGERS parties go wild these days. The main idea of them is to never let the people know who their matches are until the last minute. These are some popular practices that are storming the world's youth on this V-day. Speed dating It's exactly what the name implies. Complete with a timer, a whistle and 50 willing singles, speed dating is not the traditional dinner and a movie type of first date. Singles pay US $35 for three minutes with more than two dozen future dates. They ask questions and try to get to know each other. At the sound of a whistle, they do the same thing all over again--25 times in all. Lock and key party Women are given a lock and men are given a key, upon arriving at the party. Each key and lock has several matches. One can hunt for his/her later-to-be sweetheart in ...\n\nQ: If you go to the Dinner in the dark,   _  .", "options": ["you have to wear night vision glasses", "you have to eat with your hands", "guests eat all the courses in the darkness", "your dining partners will help you choose the food"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2779, "question": "Hunan Satellite TV is losing its leading position? There's reason for saying this. In 2012, the reality talent show , the voice of China, on the Zhejiang Television became the most popular program in China. The reaon for its popularity was really because its excellent quality? Or can we assume that without any opponent, we can't tell a contestant is winning because he is really talented or because there's no comparison? The administrative department really contributed a lot in the popularity of the voice of China. In the past, there was no other draft shows ranked as high as Super GirlandSuper Boy. Even though there were some draft shows which seemed to share the popularity, it never turned out ture. All the other draft shows were shodowed by the ones on Hunan TV. One example was that sinc...\n\nQ: The passage mainly tells us   _", "options": ["the draft shows of Hunan Satellite TV still cause our attention", "the voice of Chinais not a real draft show", "the reasons for Hunan Satellite TV is losing its leading position", "the advantages of the voice of China"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3056, "question": "Trapped on the 37thFloor Melinda Skaar wasn't expecting any phone calls. Skaar was working late in her office at the First Internet bank of California. By 10:45 that night she was almost ready to go home when the phone rang. Picking it up, she heard a guard shouting. There is a fire! Get out of there. Skaar didn't panic. She figured that it was just a small fire. Her office building was huge. There were 62 floors and her desk was on the 37thfloor. Skaar called out to office mate Stephen Oksas, who also stayed late to work. But when they got out to the hallway, they were met by a cloud of black smoke. Rushing back, Skaar shut the door and filled the space at the bottom of the door with her jacket to keep the smoke out. Then they called 911. before they could call their families, however, th...\n\nQ: What did Skaar and Oksas do where were stopped by the fire?", "options": ["they called their families", "they waited where they were", "they tried to run down the stairs", "they rushed back and shut the door"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1970, "question": "For some people, the prospect of starting college, especially going away to school, is scary. It's probably the first time that you'll be totally responsible for your own schedule. What if you intend to go to college but just don't feel ready to start yet-for whatever reason-and you don't want to take on a full-time job after graduation? You might want to take a year off to pause and regroup. This practice is common in some countries, like the United Kingdom, where it's called a \" _ \". Taking time off doesn't mean you should ignore the idea of applying to college. In fact, you may want to consider making your college plans before you become involved in other things, especially if you'll be travelling. Apply to schools and make your choice, then ask for a deferred admission. Rachel took a y...\n\nQ: Which of the following is NOT the benefit of taking a year off?", "options": ["You'll learn some great life skills.", "You'll make full preparation for starting college.", "You'll earn much money by taking on a full-time job.", "You'll gain a wonderful learning experience by joining in a volunteer organization."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 928, "question": "London Heathrow is the biggest airport in the UK, and it also handles more international passenger traffic than any other airport in the world. For this reason, enlargement was planned and on 27th March a fifth terminal opened to help to deal with the many passengers that pass through the airport. The new terminal has taken a long time to plan and build. The idea was first proposed back in the 1980s. The opening of it has been talked about widely in the media in the UK and expectations were high for the PS4.3 billion project. However, in spite of long preparations at Terminal 5 ahead of the grand opening, things soon went into a mess. There were problems from the very beginning as staff had difficulties finding car parking spaces and getting through security to get into the building. This ...\n\nQ: What was the difficulty that passengers met with on the very first day of the opening?", "options": ["It was difficult for them to find the right car parking spaces.", "It took too long to get through security to get into the building.", "They were not familiar with the new systems in the building.", "They had to wait a long time and play catch-up when checking in."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1701, "question": "When 15-year-old Louisa Ball takes a nap, she sleeps for days on end, and no amount of shaking can fully wake her up. The British girl has a rare condition called Sleeping Beauty Sickness. Doctors don't know what causes it or how to cure it --only know that it strikes teenagers and goes away by itself after eight to 12 years. Louisa's mum, Lottie, told NBC News that the girl had flulike symptoms just over a year ago. Shortly afterward, she had her first period of long sleeping. She was eventually diagnosed with Kleine-Levin Syndrome, whose victims worldwide may number no more than 1,000. The victims live normally for weeks or months at a time, with normal sleep patterns and normal energy levels. Then, with little warning, they'll go to sleep for days or weeks at a time. So far, Louisa's lo...\n\nQ: What is the best title of the passage?", "options": ["What is Narcolepsy", "How Louisa Overcame the Difficulty", "Rare Illness Turns a Girl into a \"Sleeping Beauty\"", "The Latest Research on Kleine-Levin Syndrome."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 257, "question": "Shopping in the United States changes a lot.About ninety years ago most people shopped in small stores that were owned by one person or a family.Women went from the bakery to the butcher's to the grocer and on to the fruit and vegetable seller in order to get their food for the week. Then about sixty years ago, supermarkets were born.In a supermarket, people could get all the different kinds of food they needed without going to different stores. The next big change in shopping in the United States was the shopping mall.A shopping mall is a group of stores under one roof.Because malls allowed people to shop without worrying about the weather, they soon became very popular.The mall became a place for people to socialize in addition to shopping.If you walk through a mall, you will see older p...\n\nQ: Which is the place for people to spend time with others according to the passage?", "options": ["Shopping malls", "Small stores", "Supermarkets", "Superstores"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3310, "question": "It is amazing to note that the Internet is still such a new device, and yet it is one of the fastest and most powerful media tools. But think about it for a moment. On the Internet, a big online company can be run by two guys out of their garage. So it is only reasonable that people shopping on the Net would be a little _ of the security levels. Internet giants such as Microsoft knew consumer confidence was the key to getting virtual shopping off the ground, and they work hard to make people feel safe to shop online. Credit card companies, too, quickly saw the potential for Internet shopping, and have installed things like online shopping insurance for people. If you ever have a problem with your online credit purchases, many credit card companies will happily refund your money and then se...\n\nQ: Which group of words would the writer use to describe current Internet shopping?", "options": ["Adventurous, enjoyable, fast, unreal.", "Unsafe, cheap, slow, convenient.", "Reliable, popular, convenient, slow.", "Safe, convenient, fast, comfortable."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1972, "question": "Pets are popular. They're good listeners, they encourage us to exercise, and they're always on our side when we argue with others. They can bring people comfort and pleasure. But it is important to keep in mind that pets can carry diseases that can make you sick. Washing your hands often -- especially after you touch, feed, or clean up a pet -- is the best way to keep yourself healthy and prevent the spread of disease. Be sure to clean your fingernails carefully every time you wash. You also can protect your health by wearing gloves while cleaning animal cages or cat litter boxes. Avoid washing your pet in the bathtub , but if you do, always disinfect the tub immediately afterward. Be sure to bring your pet to the hospital for examinations every two weeks or month and whenever your pet is ...\n\nQ: Which is the RIGHT way to feed your pet?", "options": ["Sharing your chocolate with your dog.", "Letting your dog drink from the toilet.", "Feeding your little cat with raw meat.", "Giving your cat cooked fish."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 893, "question": "Going on a road trip? The St. Louis Arch, Statue of Liberty, and Golden Gate Bridge are common great tourist sites. If you prefer offbeat places, check out the following roadside attractions. World's Largest Ball of Paint Alexandria, Ind. In 1977, Michael Carmichael set out to create the biggest ball of paint anywhere. Starting with a baseball as centre, he painted layer by layer of paint day after day, year after year. The ball weighs more than 1,300 pounds, with more than 20,000 coats of paint, which is recognized by Guinness World Record. Visitors can paint the wall themselves and become part of the history. The Museum of Dirt Boston, Mass. The museum is the idea of Glenn Johnson. Labeled glass bottles contain such treasures as dirt from the Great Wall of China, as well as sand from a d...\n\nQ: From the text, we can learn that   _  .", "options": ["Michael will never stop painting the large ball.", "people need to pay for visiting the Museum of Dirt.", "Paper House was completely made of paper", "Barry founded the Mustard Museum.."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2801, "question": "Any mistake made in the printing of a stamp raises its value to stamp collectors. A mistake on one inexpensive postage stamp has made the stamp worth a million and a half times its original value. The mistake was made more than a hundred years ago in the British colony of Mauritius, a small island in the Indian Ocean. In 1847 an order for stamps was sent to a London printer-Mauritius was to become the fourth country in the world to issue stamps. Before the order was filled and delivered, a ball was planned at Mauritius' Government House, and stamps were needed to send out the invitations. A local printer was instructed to copy the design for the stamps. He accidentally inscribed the words \"Post Office\" instead of \"Post Paid\" on the several hundred stamps that he printed. Today there are on...\n\nQ: Stamp collectors have paid 16 800 for   _  .", "options": ["fourteen One Penny Orange-Reds", "twelve Two Penny Blues", "one One Penny Orange-Red", "one Two Penny Blue"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2147, "question": "Many parents watch the news or other shows as children play nearby. But new research shows that even when the television is just background noise,it may be to a child's normal development. It's estimated that 75 percent of very young children in the United States live in homes where the television is on most of the time,even though the kids often aren't watching it. The University of Massachusetts researchers recently studied how TV background noise might affect young children. The study looked at 50 1,2and 3yearolds. Each child came to a lab with a parent and was allowed to play for an hour with various toys. For half the time,a television was on in the room,showing the adult game show as well as advertisements. During the other half hour,the TV was turned off. As expected,the children pa...\n\nQ: We know from the passage that   _   .", "options": ["background TV noise has little effect on adults", "most young children in America live in homes exposed to TV noise", "the effect of background TV noise on children is immediate", "most parents in America wouldn't let their children watch TV"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 237, "question": "Sociable people seem to gain extra rewards from their relationships by feeling less stressed, taking better care of themselves and having less risky lifestyles, they claim. A review of studies into the impact of relationships on health found that people had a 50% better survival rate if they belonged to a wider social group. Psychologist Holt-Lunstad's team reviewed 148 studies that observed the social activities and health of 308,849 people over an average of 7.5 years. From these they worked out how death rates varied depending on how sociable a person was. Being lonely and isolated was as bad for a person's health as smoking 15 cigarettes a day or being an alcoholic. It was as harmful as not exercising and twice as bad for the health as being very fat. Holt-Lunstad said friends and fami...\n\nQ: People who have lots of friends tend to take fewer risks, mainly because   _  .", "options": ["their friends often ask them to do so", "they want to stay with their friends", "they feel they're responsible to do so", "their friends don't do so either"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2209, "question": "Christmas Day, the birthday of Jesus Christ, is the most important festival in prefix = st1 /Britainand some other countries. On Christmas Eve, people usually tell their children to put their stockings at the end of their beds before they go to sleep. Children believe Santa Claus, with the other name of Father Christmas, will come during the night and fill their stockings with Christmas presents. Actually , Father Christmas is children's father. He dresses up in a red coat and waits until children fall asleep. Then he goes into children's bedrooms, and puts small presents in their stockings. When children are no longer young, they know who Father Christmas really is. Not only children but also their parents enjoy Christmas stockings. They also have stockings. Early on the morning of Christ...\n\nQ: What do all the British children do on Christmas Eve in the story?", "options": ["They talk all the night.", "They sing and dance.", "They put their stockings at the end of their beds.", "They won't sleep until Father Christmas comes."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 121, "question": "If you go into the woods with your friends, stay with them. If you don't, you may get lost. If you do get lost, this is what you should do. Sit down and stay where you are. Don't try to find your friends -- let them find you. You can help them to find you by staying in one place. There is another way to help your friends or other people nearby to find you. Give them a signal by shouting or whistling three times. Stop. Then shout or whistle three times again. Any signal given three times is a call for help. You will be helped by others. Keep up the shouting or whistling, always three times together. When people hear you, they will know that you are not just making noise for fun. They will let you know they have heard your signal. They will give two shouts, two whistles or two gunshots. When...\n\nQ: How do you let people believe that you are not just making noise for fun?", "options": ["Stop now and then.", "Go on shouting or whistling.", "Shout over and over at the top of voice.", "Shout or whistle three times once a while."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1731, "question": "George Bernard Shaw and Winston Churchill disliked each other. It is said that the playwright once sent Churchill two tickets for the opening night of one of his plays, together with a card, which said, \"Bring a friend (if you have one).\" Churchill, however, returned the tickets with a note, which said, \"I shall be busy that evening. Please send me two tickets for the second night (if there is one).\" There is no record of whether Shaw ever sent the tickets....\n\nQ: Why didn't Churchill want the tickets for the first night?", "options": ["He didn't want to take Shaw's insult .", "The theatre would not be as crowded the second night.", "He was busy on the first night of the show.", "He couldn't find a friend to go with him the first night."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2517, "question": "A young man went to a town and worked there. He did not have a wife and a servant did the work in his house. The young man liked laughing a lot. He nailed the servant's shoes to the floor on Monday, and then laughed, because he put his feet in them and fell down. The servant was not angry, but smiled. Then the young man put brushes in his bed on Tuesday. The servant got into bed and hit the brushes with his feet. He was afraid. The young man laughed loudly again. Again the servant was not angry, but smiled. Then on Wednesday the young man said to his servant, \"You're a nice, kind man. I am not going to be unkind to you again.\" The servant smiled and said, \"And I'm not going to put any more mud from the street in your coffee.\"...\n\nQ: The young man went to a town   _  .", "options": ["to study", "to work", "to see his relative", "to spend his holiday"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 270, "question": "Should doctors ever lie to benefit their patient---to speed recovery or to cover the coming of death? In medicine as in law, government, and other lines of work, the requirements of honesty often seem dwarfed by greater needs: the need to protect from brutal news or to uphold a promise of secrecy; to advance the public interest. What should doctors say, for example, to a 46-year-old man coming in for a routine physical check up just before going on vacation with his family who, though he feels in perfect health, is found to have a form of cancer that will cause him to die within six months. Is it best to tell him the truth? If he asks, should the doctor reject that he is ill, or minimize the gravity of the illness? Should they at least hide the truth until after the family vacation? Doctor...\n\nQ: From the passage, we can learn that the author's attitude to professional deception is    _   .", "options": ["supportive", "indifferent", "oppositive", "neutral"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 407, "question": "I was brought up in the British, _ . Strong feelings aren't something you display in public. So, you can imagine that I was unprepared for the outpouring of public grief at a Chinese funeral. My editorial team leader died recently after a short illness. He was 31. The news was so unexpected that it left us all shocked and upset. A female colleague burst into tears and cried piteously at her desk. Somehow we got through the day's work. The next day was the funeral. Our big boss stepped forward to deliver a eulogy and was soon in tears. She carried on, in Chinese of course, but at the end said in English: \"There will be no more deadlines for you in heaven.\" Next came a long-term colleague who also dissolved in tears but carried on with her speech despite being almost overcome by emotion. The...\n\nQ: At the funeral,  _  .", "options": ["five individuals made speeches", "the boss's speech was best thought of", "everyone was crying out loudly", "the writer was astonished by the scene"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 200, "question": "We produce 500 billion of plastic bags in a year worldwide and they are thrown away polluting oceans, killing wildlife and getting dumped in landfills where they take up to 1000 years to decompose. Researchers have been unsuccessfully looking for a solution. The 16-year old Canadian high school student, Daniel Burd, from Waterloo Collegiate Institute, has discovered a way to make plastic bags degrade in as few as 3 months, a finding that won him first prize at the Canada-Wide Science Fair, a $10 000 prize, a $20 000 scholarship, and a chance to revolutionize a major environmental issue. Burd's strategy was simple: Since plastic does eventually degrade, it must be eaten by microorganisms . If those microorganisms could be identified, we could put them to work eating the plastic much faster ...\n\nQ: Maintaining the required temperature takes little energy because   _  .", "options": ["plastics can get hot easily", "microbes can produce heat themselves", "much carbon dioxide is produced", "the temperature can be controlled"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1525, "question": "The atmosphere and oceans are not the only parts of the environment being damaged. Rain forests are being quickly destroyed as well, and their survival is questionable. E.O. Wilson, a biologist at Harvard, called the depletion of rain forest areas \"the greatest extinction since the end of the age of dinosaurs\". Unlike some environmental issues, rain forest depletion has fortunately received significant public and media attention. Despite the opposition to the cutting down of rain forests, the problem continues. Every year, Brazil chops down an area of forest the size of the state of Nebraska. In addition to the Amazon's rain forests, many other forests are being cut down as well. In Indonesia, Zaire, Papua-new Geinea, Malaysia, Burma, the Philippines, Peru, Colombia, Bolivia, and Venezuela...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is true according to the passage?", "options": ["The author thought the oceans' survival is questionable.", "Luckily, people and mass media all paid special attention to the depletion of rain forest.", "People have stopped cutting down rain forests because of the opposition of most people.", "The United Nations says about 50 million acres of rain forests are cut down every year."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2652, "question": "Kabul,Oct.28 (Xinhuanet)--- Unknown armed men in military uniform kidnapped three staff of the United Nations in the Afghan capital city at broad daylight Thursday ,Afghan officials confirmed . \"Three armed men in military uniform _ a UN car in Baraki area ofprefix = st1 /Kabulcity early afternoon and took away three persons including two women with them, \"Rohullah, a witness at the site told Xinhua. The kidnappers also badly beat up the Afghan driver of the UN car, added Rohullah who is a lorry driver in the city. The area has been watched over by UN guards. UN officials as well as Afghan confirmed the incident but refused to provide further information. The three kidnapped , according to some officials , who are from Britain, Ireland and Kosovo, were working for the UN-sponsored Joint El...\n\nQ: What does the underline word   _  probably mean ?", "options": ["destroyed", "damaged", "stopped", "bombed"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3046, "question": "I grow up in San Pedro. My Dad was a fisherman, and he loved the sea. He had his own boat, but it was hard making a living on the sea. He worked hard and would stay out until he caught enough to feed the family. Not just enough for our family, but also for his Mom and Dad and the other kids that were still at home. Dad was a big man, and he was strong from pulling the nets and fighting the sea for his catch. When you got close to him, you smelled the ocean. When the weather was bad he would drive me to school. He would pull right up in front, and it seemed like everybody would be standing around and watching. Then he would lean over and give me a big kiss on the cheek and tell me to be a good boy. It was so embarrassing for me. Here I was twelve years old, and my Dad would lean over and ki...\n\nQ: The writher wrote the passage in order to   _  .", "options": [".tell readers about his father's love to him", "attract readers to visit his father", "give a brief introduction to himself", "ask readers to love their fathers"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 732, "question": "Vampires , creatures of myth, have been around in one form or another for centuries. Terrifying but also attractive, they are as popular in the early 21st century as ever, as the current popularity of Twilight series, and its hero Edward Cullen, show. Vampires first appeared in fiction in the 1700s; in 1895 Irish novelist Bram Stoker published Dracula, introducing the world's most famous vampire. But just what is it about these drinkers of human blood that continues to fascinate us? Speaking to Eric Lewis of the Times and Transcript website, academic Deborah Wells said that vampires are \"culturally adaptive \". \"We create very different vampires to fit different times. Edward Cullen is not the same as Count Dracula,\" she said. Different as they are, Wells believes vampires are \"the perfect ...\n\nQ: What is the vampire like in Bram Stoker's book?", "options": ["Anxious but perfect.", "Afraid of the fall of the British Empire.", "Terrifying but also attractive.", "Powerful, old and ugly."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 801, "question": "We all use money every day. It is essential because we can pay money for whatever we want.Money is recognized as banknotes and coins. However,many years ago people couldn' t go to the shop and buy what they wanted.They had to get what they wanted through the barter trade .It was really difficult,for the barter often depended on coincidence of wants.For example,the seller of grain has to find a buyer who wants to buy grain and who also could offer something the seller wants to buy.And one more example,if a wheat farmer needs what a fruit farmer produces,a direct exchange is impossible because seasonal fruit would spoil before the grain harvest.The solution is to trade fruit for wheat indirectly through a third intermediate commodity ,such as cattle,salt,shells,wine.However,commodity money h...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["Function of money.", "History of money.", "Invention of money.", "Types of money."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2466, "question": "For a long time now, I've been fascinated by common phrases and their origins- and just why we say what we say. I decided to consult the experts, sort through all the research and compile the answers. Here are a few of the standouts. Q: Why do we\"tie the knot \"when we get married? A: Knots have been a common metaphor in marriage ceremonies all over the world and through time. The expression means\"to unite in manage\". In the Hindu marriage ceremony, the groom ties a ribbon around the bride's neck. In ancient Rome, the bride wore a belt that was tied in a knot. The groom would then unfasten it on their first night together as husband and wife. Q: Why do we say\"Many happy returns\"? A: The phrase is short for\"Many happy returns of the day\", which is to say,\"May this day return many times\"or\"Ma...\n\nQ: The purpose of the passage is to  _  .", "options": ["tell us some funny stories", "tell us the origins of some phrases", "tell us some interesting experiences", "tell us the history of the English language"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 367, "question": "Throughout the world, clothing has many uses. It is used to provide protection from cold. It is also worn to prevent others from seeing specific parts of one's body. However, the parts of the body that must be covered vary widely throughout the world. Some clothing is worn to provide supernatural protection. Wearing a lucky shirt to take an exam is calling for supernatural assistance. People in all cultures use clothing and other forms of bodily decoration to communicate status , intentions and other messages. In North America, we dress differently for business and various leisure activities. North American women usually are much more knowledgeable of little difference in messages communicated by clothes than men. At times, this leads to silly mistakes of understanding of female intentions...\n\nQ: From the passage, it can be inferred that  _  .", "options": ["clothing plays an important role in social activities", "words of dress are unable to communicate different messages", "dress is better than language in communicating messages", "messages communicated by clothes are the same in different cultures"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2901, "question": "Remember that goals are dreams with a timetable. Our goals are important for us to create what enriches our life. A very common attitude among people who are successful is that their success lies in their ability to provide themselves goals that are both numerous and exciting. When you think about your future,you are helping to feed a long-term goal of what you want to create. To realize your dreams,you must translate your vision into a series of actions you can take as soon as possible. You should be able to measure these results,to make sure they take you wherever you want. And this step should not be viewed lightly! Indeed,very few people set goals and concrete actions for themselves to achieve. Very few people note what they want to accomplish,and know each day whether they have indeed...\n\nQ: People can achieve success commonly in that they  _  .", "options": ["have many dreams", "are well-informed of how goals go", "think a lot about their bright future", "know what the goals are in their life"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1375, "question": "Nowadays more and more people are talking about genetically modified foods ( GM foods). GM foods develop from genetically modified organisms , which have had specific changes introduced into their DNA by genetic engineering techniques. These techniques are much more precise where an organism is exposed to chemicals to create a nonspecific but stable change. For many people, the hightech production raises all kinds of environmental, ethical, health and safety problems. Particularly in countries with long farming traditions, the idea seems against nature. In fact, GM foods are already very much a part of our lives. They were first put on the market in 1996. A third of the corn and more than half the cotton grown in the U. S. last year was the product of biotechnology, according to the Depart...\n\nQ: What's the writer's attitude towards GM foods?", "options": ["Enthusiastic.", "Cautious.", "Disapproving.", "Unbelievable."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2929, "question": "Kodak's decision to apply for bankruptcy protection is a sad, though not unexpected, turning point for a leading American corporation that pioneered consumer photography and dominated the film market for decades, but finally failed to adapt to the digital revolution. Although many attribute Kodak's downfall to \"complacency ,\" that explanation doesn't admit the efforts with which the company went to reinvent itself. Decades ago, Kodak invented the first digital camera in 1975 -- but in a fateful decision, the company chose to focus on its traditional film business. Large companies have a difficult time switching into new markets. For example, although Kodak predicted the rise of digital photography, its culture was too rooted in the successes of the past to fully welcome the future. In the ...\n\nQ: Why do large companies have difficulty switching to new markets?", "options": ["They are deeply stuck in their glorious past.", "They tend to be slow in facing new challenges.", "They are unwilling to invest in new technology.", "They find it costly to give up their existing business."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3108, "question": "In the 1960s, people asked about your astrological sign . In the 1990s, they wanted to know your website. These days, having a web address is almost as important as a street address. Your website is an electronic meeting place for your family, friends and potentially, millions of people around the world. Best of all, you may not have to spend a cent. The Web is filled with all kinds of free services and all it takes is some time and creativity. Think of your home page as the starting point of your website. Like the table of contents of a book or a magazine, the home page is the front door. Your site can have one or more pages, depending on how you design it. While web pages vary greatly in their design and content, most use a traditional magazine layout. At the top of the page is a banner ...\n\nQ: The main purpose of the passage is to tell you   _  .", "options": ["what a website is like", "how to build your own website", "how to meet people online", "what a website is made up of"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2649, "question": "Collections were the inspiration for a project at Thomas Tallis School, which formed part of the Imagine Children's Literature Festival last autumn. Each child (aged 12-13) beatified a box and wrote a story on the subject of collections to throw inside it. The boxes were spread within the Royal Festival Hall's Ballroom. Some were left empty to encourage The subject chosen by Luren was an imaginative one. \"It's a sort o f Cinderella story,\" she told me, inspired by a collection of letters from her cousin, ha the story these become love letters, burned by a creel stepmother. Lauren's best friend Charlotte is the stepmother. \"I'm in Charlotte's story too,\" says Lauren, \"and I get run over.\" Charlotte's tale was inspired by the girls' coin collection. \"We've collected foreign coins for years -...\n\nQ: From the stories by Lauren and Charlotte, we know that   _   .", "options": ["Charlotte hurt herself when getting a coin", "both of them developed their imagination", "both of tram will die in each other's stories", "Latwen's cousin posted her some love letters"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2119, "question": "Dubai, the Gulf desert city state, which is well-known for its huge projects before it was hit by the global financial crisis , on Saturday announced a new development to open the world's biggest mall and a park larger than London's Hyde Park. The ruler of the Gulf desert city state, Sheikh Mohammed bin Rashid al-Maktoum, announced the plan for a \"new city within Dubai\", according to an official statement, naming it after himself. No cost was stated for \"Mohammed bin Rashid City,\" to be carried out by his private companies, which developed many of Dubai's well-known projects, including Burj Khalifa, the world's tallest tower. The \"Mall of the World\" will attract 80 million visitors a year to become the \"largest in the world,\" said the statement, while its park will be \"30 percent bigger th...\n\nQ: The \"new city within Dubai\" will   _  .", "options": ["attract 62 million visitors a year", "become the world's tallest tower", "be named after the ruler of the state", "be the world's largest family entertainment center"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 330, "question": "Struggling in the US? Move to China! I graduated from the university with a degree of civil engineering. It is a good field but my heart was not in it. I wanted to be an actor or work in the entertainment industry...living a creative life. My choice of civil engineering was really a mistake but I realized too late. As soon as I graduated, I moved straight to Los Angeles--the home of the film and television industry! For three years, I tried to get a job in that field. I often worked as an extra in movies and TV shows--standing in the background while actors are in the foreground. This was fun for a while, but I wanted a real acting job, where I was speaking! Sadly, in Los Angeles, there is too much competition. Every race and age is represented: old, young, black, white, Asian and thousand...\n\nQ: What can we infer from the passage?", "options": ["Life is easier in the US.", "Life in China is not easy.", "There is always somewhere in the world where you can enjoy life.", "More Americans will move to China."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3065, "question": "A single letter written by Albert Einstein was sold for more than $400, 000. But could an e-mail printout or an electronic file reach similar heights? That's the question facing those who deal in the literary artifacts of public figures, as they struggle to work out how to do business in the electronic world where information can be copied and spread out more easily than ever before. \"Booksellers, collectors and libraries are already trading in digital objects,\" Joan Winterkorn, a researcher told people. When Emory University Library bought author Slaman Rushdie's archives in 2006, it received a desktop computer, three laptops, a hard drive and a smart phone along with his paper flies. And the writer John Updike, who died last month, started using computers in the 1980s, Winterkorn pointed...\n\nQ: Who doesn't think digital archives are of great value?", "options": ["Joan Winterkorn.", "Salman Rushdie.", "J. K. Rowling.", "Gordon Bell."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2058, "question": "The vast jungles of the Amazon rainforest are home to tribes mostly isolated from the outside world,whose way of life,largely unchanged for hundreds of years,is now increasingly threatened by modern civilization. Now, scientists discover they can monitor these\"uncontacted tribes\"using satellites,which would allow inexpensive and safe tracking of these tribes in order to protect them from outside threats. In order to help conserve these uncontacted Indians,researchers need accurate estimates of their populations.One way to collect this data involves flying over their villages,but such overflights are both expensive and could fill these native peoples with fear.Another strategy involves meeting individuals on the ground,but among other risks,scientists could accidentally spread disease to me...\n\nQ: What is the main idea of the text?", "options": ["Amazon tribes are disappearing.", "Scientists found isolated Amazon tribes.", "Modern civilization is threatening Amazon tribes.", "Isolated Amazon tribes are monitored with satellites."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 46, "question": "A new law helps people with disabilities. The law says that people with disabilities must be able to get into and out of all public buildings. It also says that business must offer special services to people who have special needs. Companies can not refuse to hire disabled workers. Many businesses may have to change their buildings and services. --Ramps must be built so people can get into buildings. --Movie theatres must have space for people in wheelchairs and seats for their friends to sit near them. --Elevators must have floor number in _ . This law will help millions of people. One woman who has been in a wheelchair for many years said, \"It is like a dream.\"...\n\nQ: Ramps can help people_.", "options": ["with hearing problems", "who have difficulty in using their hands", "who have difficulty in using their legs or feet", "who don't like stairs"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3278, "question": "Throughout life,change is the only thing that seems constant.Change has come to my 1ife many ways,in myself,and in my surroundings.At the same time,some things stay the same.This is when traditions are formed.I am often reminded of this by the photograph that sits by my bed. It all began with a kiss on my very first day of school.I remember dancing around the mirror,watching as my dark blue dress created a teacup around my waist.I admired the little ruffle of my shirt collar and how it matched perfectly with the trim at the bottom of my dress.I knew I would be the envy of all my classmates. But somehow,something was missing.I reached under my bed for the large box of bows ,in every color1 imaginable,that I was famous for.I picked out a white one that would match my shirt and carefully ran ...\n\nQ: What's the author's purpose of writing such a passage?", "options": ["To prove change is the only thing that seems constant.", "To show what a skilled photographer her mother was.", "To recall a family tradition on their first day of school.", "To display her beautiful look on the first day of school."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2145, "question": "On the site of the 9/11 tragedy, Irish university professor Elizabeth Stinger Keefe found an image of hope-- a wedding photo of a happy couple and their friends lay among the rubble of the Twin Towers. As a gesture of goodwill, she decided to try and reunite the picture with either its owner or a . Every year, on the anniversary of the terrorist attacks, she would make an attempt, posting the picture on social media and asking others to share it. Finally, after a remarkable 13 years, her work paid off. Thanks to the power of social media, her appeal was more widely shared than ever before. A man named Fred Mahe called Ms Keefe after the image went viral -- to tell her that he was in fact in the picture and that all six people photographed were alive and well. He said that the image belonge...\n\nQ: Why did Keefe want to keep the picture she found?", "options": ["Because it was her friend's picture.", "Because she wanted to find its owner.", "Because she herself was in the picture.", "Because it brought back good memories."], "answer": 1}]